[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Whatever Mama Yaya has planned,
I'll leave that up to her.
If there's one thing I've learned all these years,
it's that love is ultimately a decision.
Mikoy, Chiara is missing.
-She's not in the bridal car either. -Are you sure?
Maybe she just went to the bathroom.
That's possible, but…
I'll go look for Chiara.
-Let's go check! -What's happening?
-Hey! -Wait, Mikoy!
Don't you have any leads or information from your informants?
Maybe she's just a runaway bride.
Besides, Mario,
it's no longer news that the bride used to be part of the mafia.
Maybe she went back to her old life.
We also spoke to Donabel and Viktor.
The family even talked before Chiara left the hotel.
We also spoke to everyone who came into contact with Chiara.
None of them noticed anything unusual.
In fact, they all said the same thing.
That Chiara was a beautiful and excited bride.
Yes, sir. Viktor and Donabel are with us right now.
We'll be leaving soon as well.
I'll arrange for additional escorts
for your trip back to Manila to make sure you're all safe.
-Thank you, sir. -Thank you, sir.
Take care.
With Chiara suddenly disappearing,
we can't completely rule out a connection between
Where could Chiara be?
What if that was the last time we ever saw Chiara?
Don't say that, Dekyo.
We may not know where Chiara is,
but I'm sure she's perfectly safe wherever she is right now.
That's right.
Besides, she used to be a world-class assassin.
She can definitely defend herself against kidnappers.
Yes.
You're already talking about kidnappers, and we don't even have
any clear information yet.
So let's take it easy with our thoughts and our reactions.
I know we're all worried about Chiara,
but of course, we should just
relax and stay calm.
Okay.
Of all the people whose wedding outfits I've sewn,
Mikoy is the only one whose bride didn't show up.
I don't know what happened.
Remember, Chiara used to be part of the mafia.
They say, once you're in a syndicate, you're always in a syndicate.
That's how you see it.
I mean, it's hard to get out.
Do you think there's some unfinished business there?
Oh, no.
What if the rumors are true
and Chiara was kidnapped?
For now, just extend your stay there, Alex.
Keep an eye on your surroundings.
Maybe we're looking too far ahead when the answer is right within
our peripheral vision.
Besides,
I have a feeling about this Rahmboy.
Sir, Rahmboy? The vlogger?
The aspiring content creator?
Yes.
He may look harmless,
but if you look into his profile,
it's like…
it's too good to be true.
I think it could be some kind of curse or witchcraft.
Oh, please. I don't believe in that.
It's more believable that she simply changed her mind.
No, I don't think so.
Chiara looked completely head over heels in love when she
was trying on her gown.
Sure, she may be in love now,
but maybe she's having doubts about the future.
Oh, come on, you guys.
It's as if you've never experienced Chiara's kindness.
You're gossiping about her nonstop.
They are.
You too!
You know,
none of us knows what really happened.
So maybe the best thing we can do
is pray together that Chiara is safe.
We've already searched all over Albay,
but we still haven't found Chiara.
It's like she vanished into thin air.
Exactly. So what if we can't find her because…
She doesn't want to be found?
That's impossible.
What, do you think she actually planned not to show up at her own wedding?
And leave Brother Mikoy standing there like an idiot, waiting at the altar?
Chiara wouldn't do that.
She wouldn't just leave me like that.
Because we made a promise to each other.
So will you please just stop?
You're not helping.
Chiara is missing,
and she needs our help.
I don't know where to start,
but I won't stop until I bring her back here.
Whatever happens, son,
we're here to support you.
But maybe you need to get some rest first.
It's been a very long day.
But Mom, we're wasting time.
Mikoy.
The agency and the local police are all helping us.
I think Tess is right.
-You should get some rest first. -Mom!
Chiara could be in even more danger if we stop looking for her.
Mikoy.
I understand you.
I won't judge you because your concerns are valid,
as are your fears and worries.
But I want you to know,
we love Chiara too.
And we're worried about her too.
Maybe what we should do for now,
while we wait for any news,
is take care of each other.
Wait?
Dad!
If the Concordat really had something to do with Chiara's disappearance,
they're not the type to just sit around and wait.
They're criminals!
We're wasting time, Dad.
But there's also a time to rest
and regain your strength.
I'm sorry
if I don't have any good news for you,
but I want you to know that we're all on your side.
And all we want
is for you and Chiara to be okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
This is just so hard.
It's okay.
If I were in your position, I'd probably do the same thing.
But you really need to get some rest, so tomorrow,
we can resume the search.
But Dad…
Please.
As your father, please grant me this.
Get some rest.
Even just for a while.
Thank you, Dad.
I just don't know what I'll do if something bad happens to Chiara.
Nothing bad will happen to her.
Just have faith, son.
I've kept so many secrets
just so I could give our family a simple and peaceful life, Mikoy.
Sometimes,
I feel like fate is making me pay for all those things.
But how can I explain the thing that I saw earlier?
Chiara. What are you doing?
And where are you going?
It's been so hard for me to keep this from you.
But I promise you.
I'll find out the truth, son.
Hey!
Our king is giving us the silent treatment.
He comes and goes with authorization,
then returns whenever he feels like it.
Where did you go?
Hey.
Huh?
You're acting more like gangsters than the inmates in there.
Want me to put you inside?
Huh?
We're just disciplining him, sir.
Disciplining him?
Are you his father?
His mother?
Get out of my sight before I turn those uniforms of yours orange.
Get out!
I heard what happened,
and I'm here to protect you.
Is there still no news about my daughter?
Not yet, for now.
But don't worry.
Agent Alex and the others are doing everything
they can to find Chiara.
I trust Agent Alex.
She can find anything.
After all, she found me.
Anyway,
I'll patrol around for now. The guards might get suspicious
if they notice I'm keeping a close watch on you.
It's not like Chiara to just vanish into thin air.
I think something happened to her.
Mikoy.
Are you okay?
Maybe you should get some rest first, you know.
I won't rest until I find Chiara.
Even Mario hasn't stopped looking for Chiara either.
We can't find him either.
Chiara. What are you and Vicky planning?
Does Vicky have any other connection to Chiara?
Other than being her nanny?
Because it seems like my son is in danger again.
I will ensure the safety of Mikoy and my family.
I will find out the truth.
I've done everything you asked me to do.
I came here with you.
What do you mean when you say Mikoy's life would be in danger
if the wedding went through?
What's going on?
This is all Rio de Janyx's fault.
I only found out that he planned to use Mikoy's life,
his family,
and even the people he loves against you
if you went through with the marriage.
He wants you, my child.
I don't know him.
He doesn't even know me.
I've never even seen his face.
You know how these things work with royal families.
So if you become his wife,
no one will challenge him or his position anymore.
His position as the head of the Concordat will be secured.
Is he crazy?
Maybe.
I'm not marrying him. Never!
You need to become La Morte Bianca.
You need to fulfill your promise.
Take the throne.
Didn't I already tell you?
I don't want this anymore!
So why are you forcing this on me?
I'm not forcing you, my child.
He's blackmailing you.
To put an end to this,
you have to kill the person he's using to blackmail you,
or kill the blackmailer himself.
You choose.
There's too much happening.
Isn't there a better way?
But remember,
once a mafia, always a mafia.
You can't escape what's already been destined for you, my child.
What do you mean you can't find Dad Mario?
Yes, but he's probably just around here somewhere.
He's asking the police questions,
trying to get information, so, of course,
he can find Chiara, right?
What about the barangay watchmen?
Didn't they notice anything unusual?
Don't put too much faith in the people around here.
Ever since they heard that Chiara went missing,
they've been spreading all kinds of fake news.
Yes. All I care about right now is finding Chiara.
That's all.
Mikoy, can I talk to you?
Why?
Is this about Chiara?
It might be better if we talk in private.
No, it's okay.
They're family.
Why?
When I learned that you and Chiara had settled here,
I had everyone profiled and monitored,
just to make sure there wouldn't be any problems.
Have everyone here background-checked.
Everyone around Mikoy.
Everyone?
Everyone.
From Pepe to Rahmboy.
At first, we didn't find anything.
Until Mrs. Corales came along.
Mom?
When Dara did a background check on her,
she had worked for years in a part of Italy
where the Concordat has a strong presence.
At first,
we thought it might just be a coincidence.
Until we dug deeper and found that she had a connection to La Morte Bianca.
She is her personal housekeeper.
Wait.
What are you saying?
And the same goes for Rahmboy.
What about him?
This is insane!
This is such a mess!
We have reason to believe
that all this time, the Concordat has never stopped keeping an eye on you.
Then we need to do everything we can to get her back.
-It's not that easy? -You don't understand.
-Mikoy! -You listen to me!
When you asked me for help,
-I agreed. -Wait, what’s going on?
I gave everything to the agency. Everything!
-Just a second, Mikoy. -Mikoy.
-You owe me. -Calm down, Mikoy.
For all the sacrifices I've made.
Now I'm coming to collect.
-Mikoy. -The person that I love
needs my help.
Mikoy.
Dear.
Why do you look so worried?
Does Chiara really have to lead the Concordat?
You know we don't have a choice.
Chiara is the only one who can become the queen of the Concordat.
Chiara is the only one who can bring the mafia leaders to their knees.
She's so happy now.
She's happy here,
with Mikoy and the others.
Isn't she?
I was happy once too.
And that made me realize
that real happiness
isn't about being loved or loving someone.
Being at the top, where no one can bring you down.
But, Mom…
What if Chiara really doesn't want it anymore?
I'll destroy every reason she has to be happy.
I'll personally put an end to Mikoy Pinagpala.
Whose could this be?
Someone from outside!
Come on. Let's find out.
Ma'am. Sorry to bother you.
We found a motorcycle outside.
Looks like we may have an unauthorized visitor.
You need to fulfill your promise.
Take the throne.
He plans to use Mikoy's life,
his family,
even the people he loves against you
if you go through with the wedding.
You know,
this thing about royal families,
they marry for power.
So if you become his wife,
no one will challenge his position anymore.
His position as head of the Concordat will be secure.
To put an end to this,
you need to kill
whatever he's blackmailing you with,
or the blackmailer himself.
Choose.
Is this really the only way to protect you, Mikoy?
To go back to who I used to be?
-Sir Mario? -Rahmboy.
-Rahmboy. -I know.
I’m just following orders.
Rahmboy.
I have a hunch.
What hunch?
I think Dad Mario knows something.
He may have seen something or followed someone.
But why didn't he tell me?
He's trying to protect you, Mikoy.
He's trying to be a good father to you.
Chiara!
What happened?
Rio has already sent someone to kill you.
You need to do what he says!
Kill Rio.
So you and Mikoy can finally be free.
I'll handle him.
We need you here.
Let’s go.